<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<item>
		<title>mail_alter</title>
		<external>http://api.drupal.org/api/search/7/hook_mail_alter</external>
		<group>hook</group>
		<template><![CDATA[
/**
* Implements hook_mail_alter();
*/
function ${file_name}_mail_alter(&$message) {
   ${cursor}
}
]]></template>
		<help><![CDATA[<h2>hook_mail_alter(&$message)</h2>

<p>Alter an email message created with the drupal_mail() function.</p>
<p>hook_mail_alter() allows modification of email messages created and sent
with drupal_mail(). Usage examples include adding and/or changing message
text, message fields, and message headers.</p>
<p>Email messages sent using functions other than drupal_mail() will not
invoke hook_mail_alter(). For example, a contributed module directly
calling the drupal_mail_system()->mail() or PHP mail() function
will not invoke this hook. All core modules use drupal_mail() for
messaging, it is best practice but not mandatory in contributed modules.</p>

<h3>Parameters</h3>
<p><b>
$message</b> -- 
An array containing the message data. Keys in this array include:</p>
<ul>
<li>'id':
The drupal_mail() id of the message. Look at module source code or
drupal_mail() for possible id values.
</li>
<li>'to':
The address or addresses the message will be sent to. The
formatting of this string must comply with RFC 2822.
</li>
<li>'from':
The address the message will be marked as being from, which is
either a custom address or the site-wide default email address.
</li>
<li>'subject':
Subject of the email to be sent. This must not contain any newline
characters, or the email may not be sent properly.
</li>
<li>'body':
An array of strings containing the message text. The message body is
created by concatenating the individual array strings into a single text
string using "\n\n" as a separator.
</li>
<li>'headers':
Associative array containing mail headers, such as From, Sender,
MIME-Version, Content-Type, etc.
</li>
<li>'params':
An array of optional parameters supplied by the caller of drupal_mail()
that is used to build the message before hook_mail_alter() is invoked.
</li>
<li>'language':
The language object used to build the message before hook_mail_alter()
is invoked.
</li>
</ul>



]]></help>
	</item>