<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<item>
		<title>field_storage_pre_load</title>
		<external>http://api.drupal.org/api/search/7/hook_field_storage_pre_load</external>
		<group>hook</group>
		<template><![CDATA[
/**
* Implements hook_field_storage_pre_load();
*/
function ${file_name}_field_storage_pre_load($entity_type, $entities, $age, &$skip_fields, $options) {
   ${set_cursor}
}
]]></template>
		<help><![CDATA[<h2>hook_field_storage_pre_load($entity_type, $entities, $age, &$skip_fields, $options)</h2>

<p>Act before the storage backends load field data.</p>
<p>This hook allows modules to load data before the Field Storage API,
optionally preventing the field storage module from doing so.</p>
<p>This lets 3rd party modules override, mirror, shard, or otherwise store a
subset of fields in a different way than the current storage engine.
Possible use cases include per-bundle storage, per-combo-field storage, etc.</p>
<p>Modules implementing this hook should load field values and add them to
objects in $entities. Fields with no values should be added as empty
arrays. In addition, fields loaded should be added as keys to $skip_fields.</p>

<h3>Parameters</h3>
<p><b>
$entity_type</b> -- 
The type of entity, such as 'node' or 'user'.</p>
<p><b>$entities</b> -- 
The array of entity objects to add fields to, keyed by entity ID.</p>
<p><b>$age</b> -- 
FIELD_LOAD_CURRENT to load the most recent revision for all fields, or
FIELD_LOAD_REVISION to load the version indicated by each entity.</p>
<p><b>$skip_fields</b> -- 
An array keyed by field IDs whose data has already been loaded and
therefore should not be loaded again. Add a key to this array to indicate
that your module has already loaded a field.</p>
<p><b>$options</b> -- 
An associative array of additional options, with the following keys:</p>
<ul>
<li>field_id: The field ID that should be loaded. If unset, all fields
should be loaded.
</li>
<li>deleted: If TRUE, deleted fields should be loaded as well as
non-deleted fields. If unset or FALSE, only non-deleted fields should be
loaded.
</li>
</ul>



]]></help>
	</item>