<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<item>
		<title>block</title>
		<external>http://api.drupal.org/api/search/7/hook_block</external>
		<group>hook</group>
		<template><![CDATA[
/**
* Implementation of hook_block();
*/
function ${file_name}_block($op = 'list', $delta = 0, $edit = array()) {
   ${set_cursor}
}
]]></template>
		<help><![CDATA[<h2>hook_block($op = 'list', $delta = 0, $edit = array())</h2>

<p>Declare a block or set of blocks.</p>
<p>Any module can declare a block (or blocks) to be displayed by implementing
hook_block(), which also allows you to specify any custom configuration
settings, and how to display the block.</p>
<p>In hook_block(), each block your module provides is given a unique
identifier referred to as "delta" (the array key in the return value for the
'list' operation). Delta values only need to be unique within your module,
and they are used in the following ways:</p>
<ul>
<li>Passed into the other hook_block() operations as an argument to
identify the block being configured or viewed.
</li>
<li>Used to construct the default HTML ID of "block-MODULE-DELTA" applied to
each block when it is rendered (which can then be used for CSS styling or
JavaScript programming).
</li>
<li>Used to define a theming template suggestion of block__MODULE__DELTA, for
advanced theming possibilities.
</li>
</ul>
<p>The values of delta can be strings or numbers, but because of the uses above
it is preferable to use descriptive strings whenever possible, and only use a
numeric identifier if you have to (for instance if your module allows users
to create several similar blocks that you identify within your module code
with numeric IDs).</p>

<h3>Parameters</h3>
<p><b>
$op</b> -- 
What kind of information to retrieve about the block or blocks.
Possible values:</p>
<ul>
<li>'list': A list of all blocks defined by the module.
</li>
<li>'configure': Configuration form for the block.
</li>
<li>'save': Save the configuration options.
</li>
<li>'view': Process the block when enabled in a region in order to view its
contents.
</li>
</ul>
<p><b>$delta</b> -- 
Which block to return (not applicable if $op is 'list'). See above for more
information about delta values.</p>
<p><b>$edit</b> -- 
If $op is 'save', the submitted form data from the configuration form.</p>



]]></help>
	</item>