<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<item>
		<title>aggregator_parse</title>
		<external>http://api.drupal.org/api/search/7/hook_aggregator_parse</external>
		<group>hook</group>
		<template><![CDATA[
/**
* Implements hook_aggregator_parse().
*/
function ${file_name}_aggregator_parse($feed) {
   ${cursor}
}
]]></template>
		<help><![CDATA[<h2>hook_aggregator_parse($feed)</h2>

<p>Implement this hook to create an alternative parser for aggregator module.</p>
<p>A parser converts feed item data to a common format. The parser is called
at the second of the three aggregation stages: data is downloaded by the
active fetcher, it is converted to a common format by the active parser and
finally, it is passed to all active processors which manipulate or store the
data.</p>
<p>Modules that define this hook can be set as active parser on
admin/config/services/aggregator. Only one parser can be active at a time.</p>

<h3>Parameters</h3>
<p><b>
$feed</b> -- 
The $feed object that describes the resource to be parsed.
$feed->source_string contains the raw feed data as a string. Parse data
from $feed->source_string and expose it to other modules as an array of
data items on $feed->items.</p>
<p>Feed format:</p>
<ul>
<li>$feed->description (string) - description of the feed
</li>
<li>$feed->image (string) - image for the feed
</li>
<li>$feed->etag (string) - value of feed's entity tag header field
</li>
<li>$feed->modified (UNIX timestamp) - value of feed's last modified header
field
</li>
<li>$feed->items (Array) - array of feed items.
</li>
</ul>
<p>By convention, the common format for a single feed item is:
$item[key-name] = value;</p>
<p>Recognized keys:
TITLE (string) - the title of a feed item
DESCRIPTION (string) - the description (body text) of a feed item
TIMESTAMP (UNIX timestamp) - the feed item's published time as UNIX timestamp
AUTHOR (string) - the feed item's author
GUID (string) - RSS/Atom global unique identifier
LINK (string) - the feed item's URL</p>



]]></help>
	</item>