<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<item>
		<title>requirements</title>
		<external>http://api.drupal.org/api/search/7/hook_requirements</external>
		<group>hook</group>
		<template><![CDATA[
/**
* Implements hook_requirements().
*/
function ${file_name}_requirements($phase) {
   ${cursor}
}
]]></template>
		<help><![CDATA[<h2>hook_requirements($phase)</h2>

<p>Check installation requirements and do status reporting.</p>
<p>This hook has three closely related uses, determined by the $phase argument:</p>
<ul>
<li>Checking installation requirements ($phase == 'install').
</li>
<li>Checking update requirements ($phase == 'update').
</li>
<li>Status reporting ($phase == 'runtime').
</li>
</ul>
<p>Note that this hook, like all others dealing with installation and updates,
must reside in a module_name.install file, or it will not properly abort
the installation of the module if a critical requirement is missing.</p>
<p>During the 'install' phase, modules can for example assert that
library or server versions are available or sufficient.
Note that the installation of a module can happen during installation of
Drupal itself (by install.php) with an installation profile or later by hand.
As a consequence, install-time requirements must be checked without access
to the full Drupal API, because it is not available during install.php.
For localization you should for example use $t = get_t() to
retrieve the appropriate localization function name (t() or st()).
If a requirement has a severity of REQUIREMENT_ERROR, install.php will abort
or at least the module will not install.
Other severity levels have no effect on the installation.
Module dependencies do not belong to these installation requirements,
but should be defined in the module's .info file.</p>
<p>The 'runtime' phase is not limited to pure installation requirements
but can also be used for more general status information like maintenance
tasks and security issues.
The returned 'requirements' will be listed on the status report in the
administration section, with indication of the severity level.
Moreover, any requirement with a severity of REQUIREMENT_ERROR severity will
result in a notice on the the administration overview page.</p>

<h3>Parameters</h3>
<p><b>
$phase</b> -- 
The phase in which requirements are checked:</p>
<ul>
<li>install: The module is being installed.
</li>
<li>update: The module is enabled and update.php is run.
</li>
<li>runtime: The runtime requirements are being checked and shown on the
status report page.
</li>
</ul>



]]></help>
	</item>