<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<item>
		<title>filter_info</title>
		<external>http://api.drupal.org/api/search/7/hook_filter_info</external>
		<group>hook</group>
		<template><![CDATA[
/**
* Implements hook_filter_info().
*/
function ${file_name}_filter_info() {
   ${cursor}
}
]]></template>
		<help><![CDATA[<h2>hook_filter_info()</h2>

<p>Define content filters.</p>
<p>User submitted content is passed through a group of filters before it is
output in HTML, in order to remove insecure or unwanted parts, correct or
enhance the formatting, transform special keywords, etc. A group of filters
is referred to as a "text format". Administrators can create as many text
formats as needed. Individual filters can be enabled and configured
differently for each text format.</p>
<p>This hook is invoked by filter_get_filters() and allows modules to register
input filters they provide.</p>
<p>Filtering is a two-step process. First, the content is 'prepared' by calling
the 'prepare callback' function for every filter. The purpose of the 'prepare
callback' is to escape HTML-like structures. For example, imagine a filter
which allows the user to paste entire chunks of programming code without
requiring manual escaping of special HTML characters like < or &amp;. If the
programming code were left untouched, then other filters could think it was
HTML and change it. For many filters, the prepare step is not necessary.</p>
<p>The second step is the actual processing step. The result from passing the
text through all the filters' prepare steps gets passed to all the filters
again, this time with the 'process callback' function. The process callbacks
should then actually change the content: transform URLs into hyperlinks,
convert smileys into images, etc.</p>
<p>For performance reasons content is only filtered once; the result is stored
in the cache table and retrieved from the cache the next time the same piece
of content is displayed. If a filter's output is dynamic, it can override the
cache mechanism, but obviously this should be used with caution: having one
filter that does not support caching in a particular text format disables
caching for the entire format, not just for one filter.</p>
<p>Beware of the filter cache when developing your module: it is advised to set
your filter to 'cache' => FALSE while developing, but be sure to remove that
setting if it's not needed, when you are no longer in development mode.</p>




]]></help>
	</item>