<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
	<item>
		<title>filter_FILTER_settings</title>
		<external>http://api.drupal.org/api/search/7/hook_filter_FILTER_settings</external>
		<group>hook</group>
		<template><![CDATA[
/**
* Implements hook_filter_FILTER_settings();
*/
function ${file_name}_filter_FILTER_settings($form, &$form_state, $filter, $format, $defaults, $filters) {
   ${set_cursor}
}
]]></template>
		<help><![CDATA[<h2>hook_filter_FILTER_settings($form, &$form_state, $filter, $format, $defaults, $filters)</h2>

<p>Settings callback for hook_filter_info().</p>
<p>Note: This is not really a hook. The function name is manually specified via
'settings callback' in hook_filter_info(), with this recommended callback
name pattern. It is called from filter_admin_format_form().</p>
<p>This callback function is used to provide a settings form for filter
settings, for filters that need settings on a per-text-format basis. This
function should return the form elements for the settings; the filter
module will take care of saving the settings in the database.</p>
<p>If the filter's behavior depends on an extensive list and/or external data
(e.g. a list of smileys, a list of glossary terms), then the filter module
can choose to provide a separate, global configuration page rather than
per-text-format settings. In that case, the settings callback function
should provide a link to the separate settings page.</p>

<h3>Parameters</h3>
<p><b>
$form</b> -- 
The prepopulated form array of the filter administration form.</p>
<p><b>$form_state</b> -- 
The state of the (entire) configuration form.</p>
<p><b>$filter</b> -- 
The filter object containing the current settings for the given format,
in $filter->settings.</p>
<p><b>$format</b> -- 
The format object being configured.</p>
<p><b>$defaults</b> -- 
The default settings for the filter, as defined in 'default settings' in
hook_filter_info(). These should be combined with $filter->settings to
define the form element defaults.</p>
<p><b>$filters</b> -- 
The complete list of filter objects that are enabled for the given format.</p>



]]></help>
	</item>